http://www.2harvest.org/about_us/privacy-policy/

Donate
Many features of this site require JavaScript. Learn how to enable javascript.
Privacy Policy
Second Harvest Heartland has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our organization, including the website located at the URL www.2harvest.org.
In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. Second Harvest Heartland reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of:
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected and how it is collected
Who collects such information
How such information is used
With whom your information may be shared
What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information
What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control
How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Second Harvest Heartland by sending an email to communications@2harvest.org. Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
Personal Information Collection and Use
Our offline and online (via the website) registration forms for events, activities, and donations require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, email format preference (e.g. HTML vs. Text), mailing address, telephone number, employer, personal interests, demographic information, personal payment information and other similar data. Second Harvest Heartland respects your desire for privacy and handles any information you provide with care. The only personal data we gather from you is that which you voluntarily provide. If you do choose to provide us with personal information voluntarily through any form that is currently available, this information will not be sold or rented to other organizations or companies. We may use your personal information to contact you in the future.
Internet Protocol (IP) Address
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Use of "Cookies"
Our website may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our website. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes Web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.
Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.
Security
All information provided to the Second Harvest Heartland website is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Second Harvest Heartland. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
Tell-A-Friend
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our website, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Second Harvest Heartland will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the website. Second Harvest Heartland stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
Other Websites
Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Second Harvest Heartland has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our organization and our website, or your dealings with our organization and our website, you can contact:
Phone: 651-484-5117
Second Harvest Heartland
7101 Winnetka Avenue N. Brooklyn Park, MN 55428
You can also send an email to: communications@2harvest.org
Take action now.
Donate
Volunteer
Participate
